

# **Contact**



+57 302 271 9698



mayorcajeronimo@gmail.com



<u> mayorcajeronimo.dev</u>

# **Education**

## Bootcamp at **Porter Metrics**

Software Development Jan - Nov 2022

## **Universidad de Caldas**

Systems Engineering Ago 2022 - Jun 2024

# References

### **Alexis Gomez**

**Porter Metrics** (57) 312 768 6118

# Languages

Spanish (native) English (fluid)

# **JERONIMO** MAYORCA

# **Junior Dev**

### **ABOUT ME**

I am a junior fullstack developer with 2+ years of experience, aiming to specialize in backend development. Throughout my career, I have worked on numerous projects that have enhanced my technical and teamwork skills, providing me with a deep understanding of the software development lifecycle.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Kevin's Jewelry (May 2024 - Jul 2024)

- Developed a website for a jewelry wholesaler in collaboration with two friends.
- Technologies used: Angular, FuseTheme, NestJS, PostgreSQL.
- Implemented a registration system and access to a catalog with special prices for resellers.

## Software Developer at Humphreysoft (Jul 2023 - Mar 2024)

- Responsibilities: Contribute to the development of a new module for the app, support, fix printing formats and front-end issues, modify the API, and conduct API testing with Postman, create sites for new customers.
- Technologies used: Python, Frappe Framework, SSH servers, REST/SOAP APIs, Docker, Postman, Linux.
- Achievements: Integrated an instant chat with ZOHO in order to improve the user-experience asking support, contributed to the integration of a module for sending equivalent documents to DIAN, and fixed some API troubles.

## Software Technician at PC Tintas (Nov 2022 - Feb 2023)

· Responsibilities: Receiving and repairing customer equipment, managing inventory, and providing customer service.